unfollowerstats.com 2018-01-29

# Privacy Policy :: Track and unfollow your unfollowers! :: Unfollower Stats

> **Privacy Policy for UNFOLLOWERSTATS.COM**
> 
> The privacy of our visitors to UNFOLLOWERSTATS.COM is important to us.
> 
> Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. 
> 
>   * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
>   * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
>   * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
>   * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
>   * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
>   * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification. 
>   * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 
> 

> 
> We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained. 
> 
> At UNFOLLOWERSTATS.COM, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit UNFOLLOWERSTATS.COM, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.
> 
> **Log Files**
> 
> As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.
> 
> **Cookies and Web Beacons**
> 
> We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.
> 
> We also use third party advertisements on UNFOLLOWERSTATS.COM to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).
> 
> **DoubleClick DART cookies**
> 
> We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).
> 
> The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.
> 
> You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/preferences?hl=en>
> 
> You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
> 
> Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.
